嘿
Hey, Mom.
你是在哪遇到他的
Hey! Where did you find this stranger?
在路上遇到的
Found him on the road.
我可以借用一下你的 我要s去上班
Is it okay if I use your car? I really need to get to work.
- 好的 - 嗯
- Sure. - Yeah?
你想不想留下砀我一起吃c
You don't wanna stay and help us finish off the last of Bambi with this stew?
我也想的 但我得走了 爸 xx了
I'd love to, I have to go. Dad, thank you.
路上小心
Have a good one.
怎N
How was it?
不算太糟
Yeah, wasn't too bad.
嘿
Hey...
你今天晚上要l言了
you're gonna have to say a few words tonight.
要f多少
How many?
@嘛
Well...
林肯的《葛底斯堡演f》有282~
Lincoln did, what, 282 for the Gettysburg Address.
那你演v就花100~啊
So, 100?
e@ 他只是想o你C表示感x
Come on, they're just trying to thank you.
又不是要你面π行剃
It's not gonna be a firing squad.
很快就Y束的吧
That would be over quick, though.
@是新的
Is that new?
不
No.
@YB好
Just tuck it there.
我@人不擅L做演v
Um, I'm... I'm no speech giver.
能x榛W市年度秀市民 我非常s幸
But I sure as heck am very honored to be named Kehoe's Citizen of the Year.
如果要我Q定的
However, if... if it were up to me...
我把@Co我X得更得的人
I'd give it to somebody more important.
我只是...
Uh... I'm a...
我只是一位
I'm just a guy who keeps a strip
榇笱┧困的市民的_路者
of civilization open through the wilderness for people.
有r候
When you...
你日鸵蝗 _^同一l路
when you drive the same road day after day,
走一l你]走^的路 @拥南敕ê苋菀壮霈F在你的X海Y
it's... easy to start thinking about the road not taken.
我M量自己不去那N想
I try not to do that. You see...
我\夂芎
I was lucky.
我x定了一l路
I picked a good road early...
就猿肿呦氯
and I stayed on it.
小子 今天感X如何
Hey, kid. How was your day?
e
Easy!
P
Kyle. Kyle!
]嘴
Shut up!
- ]嘴 - 救命
- Help! - Shut up!
抓住他的手
Get his arms!
- 抓住他的皮 - 抓住了
- Get his belt! - I got it.
拉下
Pull it down.
救命
Help!
的
Shit.
冷酷追
丹佛
- 怎N了 - 我不想去
- What's going on? - I don't wanna go.
我知道你小子U明 但有r候也犯傻啊
Hey, I know you're smart but you're not that smart.
- 他不想去 - 的
- Doesn't wanna go. - Ah, shit.
我聿虏 是不是蒂姆又邮至
Let me guess, this is about Tim, right?
瑞恩班上有位喊
Ryan's got a bully in his class.
蒂姆昨天把他揍得嘴啃泥
Tim rubbed his face in the dirt yesterday.
遇到喊圆豢膳
Do you know what a bully is?
@是C明你是男子h的C
It's a chance to prove your mettle.
@NC不多得 可不能放^
Now, you don't wanna waste those chances in life.
- 他K^比我大 - 那更好
- He's a lot bigger than I am. - Yeah, even better.
你是f我去揍他N
Are you saying I should hit him?
先@N手挺好的
Yeah, for a start.
- 我X得@不是好主意 - 怎Nf
- That's not a very good idea. - Oh yeah, why not?
因槟俏揖透他一哟懒
Because then I'll be as stupid as he is.
快 ^
Listen... come here, come here.
你^生日的r候 我送了你一本王作樯日Y物
I gave you Lord of the Flies for your birthday.
我估你]_始x吧
I'll bet you haven't even started it yet.
那真是太糟了
Well, then that's too bad.
你想知道的那些事 答案都可以在那本中找到
All the answers you'll ever need are in that book.
好了 是r候去上W了
Come on, time to go.
你昨天晚上真是蚩褚暗陌
You were a real wild man last night.
- ]l比你更牛了 - 大家都不知道你跳舞啊
- There's no one crazier than you, buddy. - Who knew you could dance.
- 很爽吧 - 跟你f 下次我再
- Ah, good times, huh? - Tell you what, we'll do this again, huh.
你馍不e 吃c早吧
You look good. Get you some breakfast.
我的天
Jesus, Grace.
住 企w放M去的r候 ^朝外
@是你的鹤
Your son?
他死於可卡因吸食^量
He died of a heroin overdose.
打_一下
Um, excuse me.
我鹤P他不是a君子
Kyle wasn't a druggie.
很多孩子的父母都@Nf
Sorry, but all the parents say that.
但是他真的是聿晃毒的
But he... he wasn't a druggie.
接下硪怎Nk
What... what are you gonna do?
@案子要w毒分局管了
I'll be turning it over to Vice and Narcotics.
我都不t解自己的鹤
We didn't know our own son.
P不是a君子
Kyle wasn't a druggie.
你你f的@些
You're not listening!
他使我的`魂d醒 樽约旱拿引我走x路
He leadeth me to the paths of righteousness for His name's sake.
我m然行^死a的幽谷
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
也不怕遭害 因槟闩c我同在
I shall fear no evil for thou art with me...
你用油膏了我的^
Thou anointest my head with oil.
使我福杯M溢
My cup runneth over.
我一生一世
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me
必有恩惠慈垭S著我
all the days of my life.
我要住在耶和A的殿中 直到永h
And I shall dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
尼斯
Nels?
但丁
Dante?
我很抱歉 尼斯
I'm sorry, Nels.
很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
本聿是@拥
It wasn't supposed to end like this.
我知道那些在哪 什Nr候到
I know where and when the cocaine arrives.
P@些事都不知情 真的
Kyle didn't know about any of this. That's the truth.
就一包而已
It was just one bag.
Just one bag!
但那些人 一直追⑽
But people like that, they always find out.
慢著 慢著 你f的是什N人
Wait a minute, wait a minute. What people?
你f的是什N人
What people do you mean?
你身上有F金
Do you have... do you have any cash?
- 他抓到我 就折磨我的 - 什N人
- If they find me, they'll hurt me! - What people!
- 求求你 求求你 - 你f的是什N人
- Please! Please! - What people do you mean?
斯皮多 那人叫斯皮多
Speedo, there's a guy named Speedo.
- 是叫斯皮多吧 - 我只JR@位毒
- Speedo? - He's the only one I know!
我去哪能找到@砘
Just tell me where I can find this guy
告V我 然後你soL
and then you get the hell out of here!
他在哪
Where is he?
你就是斯皮多吧
So, you're Speedo?
]e 老^
Bingo, gold star.
但丁我砀你打招呼
Dante says hello.
我不JR什N叫但丁的人
I don't know any Dantes.
你JR的
Yes, you do.
他跟我的鹤 P 一起在基WC龉ぷ
He worked at the Kehoe airport with my son... Kyle.
你也JR我鹤Π
You know him too.
P
Kyle?
嗯 你是f@P是你鹤影
Oh, yeah. Kyle, that's your kid?
@影 抱歉 我不JR
Yeah, yeah, I, uh... No, I don't know him. Sorry.
我JR的名字叫P的人多了去了
I know a lot of people, I know a lot of... Kyles.
告V我究竟是怎N回事
Tell me what happened.
告V我
Tell me.
老^ 看那 T在那
All right, Pops. There's the door, all right?
我不管你是哪淼 建h你是打道回府吧
I don't know what igloo you crawled out of but I think it's time you crawled back in.
相信我 你最好乖乖按我f的做
And trust me, that's your, uh, best move.
懂了]
Okay?
你拿到了我手C
You have my phone?
告V我究竟是怎N回事
Tell me what happened.
我只是
I was...
我只是替人只疃已
I was just taking orders.
替l只
Taking orders from who?
l
Who!
林博
- Limbo. - Huh?
- 林博 - 林博
- Limbo. - Limbo?
林博
Limbo.
Limbo...
是@位N @叫林博的N
Is that him? That Limbo?
斯皮多
毫o疑 丹・YS斯在所有教中能排到前三
No doubt about it, Dan Reeves was at least in the top three best coaches.
我在回Y高球龅谋荣^往
And since we're strolling down memory lane at the Mile High Stadium,
F在想丹佛市的一}
here's a late night question for you, Denver.
v史上最的四分l 是埃威是曼
Greatest quarterback ever, Elway or Manning?
如果您想回答@} 艽555-2395
Give me a call on 555-2395.
埃威
Elway.
你怎N不我去哪了
Aren't you gonna ask where I've been?
斯皮多失了
Uh, Speedo's missing.
斯皮多是哪位
Who's Speedo?
我的一人 但估你不JR的
One of my employees. But you wouldn't know about him,
因槲送孩子上W的路上 不公事 你懂@的吧
because we don't talk about business on the way to school, do we?
@是l放M淼
Who packed these?
- 吃一c]事的吧 - @可是玉米糖{ 果糖含量高
- Didn't think a treat would kill him. - High fructose corn syrup.
卵磷脂
Lecithin.
小K打
Baking soda?
@玩意就是老鼠
The only thing not in those is rat poison.
我跟你f
I want you to know...
我不知道@是什N情r
I had no hand in this.
我X得毒品合法化
I say make them all legal.
甲安菲他明 f片@些
Meth, ex, opium.
要我f 商ｉT_店面uf片
An opium den in every mall, that's my platform.
人想要@些就提供o他 然後狠狠收 我工Y翻番
Give the people what they want. Tax the shit out of it, then double our pay.
- 你X得我的想法怎N  - 是算了吧
- What do you think about that? - No thanks.
我希望我能分得清那些是好人 那些是娜
I wanna be able to tell the good guys from the bad guys. That way I'll know who to shoot.
那位是尼斯・考曼
Nels Coxman.
@得年度最佳市民Q
Citizen of the Year.
祝他好\
Good for him.
世界很酷的 你知道吧 」靠「曼
It's a real word, you know, cocksman.
意思是」床上功夫了得的男人「
It means "a man adept at the art of fornication."
vS段子的功力了得
Nice.
看到了那些砘稂N
You see these guys?
那只是大麻而已
It's just weed.
大麻I是合法的 在家吸食也是合法的
Yeah, it's legal to purchase, legal to smoke at home.
深呼吸 戆 呼吸 放
Take a breath. Come on, breathe.
如果你想^m在基W市的谭ú块T工作下去
There's a principle you need to get on board with
有些事情你是得W的
if you intend to survive and advance in Kehoe law enforcement.
我把它Q作「看情r谭ā
It's called community policing.
我考]社^Y的F 再M行谭
Wherein we embrace and enforce the values of our community.
社^Y的F罹褪撬朝我Q中指 不能管管N
The values of them giving us the finger?
我@是滑雪俚 人磉@是滑雪的 打打炮 嗑大麻 嗨起
We're a ski town. Folks come here to ski, have sex and get high.
e搞得那No
So lighten up.
你想查c大案子是吧
Here, you wanna get your Dirty Harry on?
@些案子]幽
The meter just hit zero.
e吃口香糖了
Get rid of the gum.
那N 有什N需要我椭的 先生
So, what can I do for you, boss?
好的
Uh, I'm...
稍後
I'll be right with you.
- 真是y以置信 - 等我一
- Just can't believe this is happening. - Give me one second.
Q定好了
What's the verdict back here?
真是美O了
It's absolutely stunning.
真是y以置信
Hmm. Yeah, I can't believe this.
我喜g@蕾z的和形
I love the detail in the lace. The shape.
- 很美吧 - 是的
- It's so elegant, right? - Yes.
我非常喜g 我就x@件了
No, I absolutely love it. I think this is it.
- 真是美哭了 - 哭了就不好看了
- I think I'm gonna cry. - It's so stupid.
你看起碚媸
You look absolutely...
面就不~外收M了
I'll throw in the veil at no extra charge.
- 恭喜 - 非常感x你所做的@些
- Congratulations. - Thanks for everything.
感X就像做粢
It feels surreal.
老 有什N需要我椭的
All right. How can I help you, boss?
我想I一件晚Y服
Uh, I'm, uh, I'm looking for a tux.
好的 什Nr候ek婚Y
You got it. When is the wedding?
不是婚Y用的
It's not a wedding. My...
我和我妻子要重申婚s
my wife and I, we're renewing our vows.
夫妻PS不e啊
Still going strong, huh?
我就希望夫D都恩勰
That's what I like to hear.
- 我先砹恳幌履愕某叽a吧 - 好的
- How's about we get you measured, huh? - Sure.
你⒘宋鹤
You killed my boy.
l你下手的
Who told you to do it?
l
Who?
杉塔 杉塔
Santa. Santa.
- 杉塔是l - @是他的b
- "Santa"? - That's what he goes by.
我要怎N才能找到他
Where can I find this "Santa"?
基W市有一座小C
There's a little airport in Kehoe.
他坐wC把\^ 然後еXx_
He flies in with the coke and out with the money.
他L什N
What does he look like?
他L得像}Q老人
He looks like a Santa.
求求你 不要 求求你
No! Come on, please. You don't have to do that. Come on, please.
埃威是曼
Elway or Manning?
你f什N
What?
v史上最害的四分l 你x埃威是曼
Greatest quarterback ever. Elway or Manning?
埃威
Elway.
雅各布・特曼 「林博」
你知道P_通了~N
Did you know Kyle had a Facebook?
你知道他最喜g的逢是哪N
Do you know his favorite band?
他l的B提到了他最喜g的影 你知道
He posted his favorite movies, do you know those?
你^一起去打C旅行的事啊
What'd the two of you talk about on your damn hunting trips?
打C啊
Hunting.
他的
Damn it.
Goddamn.
他的
Damn it!
@都是你弄G的第四健身包了
That's the fourth gym bag you've lost.
你就站在@c凳前
Yeah, but who's counting, right?
你可能不信 但比起算我G了健身包
You might find this hard to believe
我有更重要的事要做
but I've got more important things to do than keep track of gym bags.
比如f我忙著赍X
Like earning the money to pay for them.
我跟你f
Tell you what...
你拿著@些X
why don't you take this
他想要多少健身包就o他I多少
and buy him every single goddamn gym bag he'll ever need.
@些
Does that work for you?
好吧
All right.
@o你
Well, that's for you.
- @是J真的吧 - 不
- Tell me this is a joke. - No.
以下是瑞恩的食 你要栏绦
That's Ryan's new diet. And you're gonna follow it to the letter.
早餐吃草牛肉 JS 腰果
Breakfast: grass-fed beef, asparagus, cashews.
午餐一拥 晚餐一拥
Lunch, the same. Dinner, the same.
L一吃那些 L二Q一下 u肉 花椰菜 煎蛋
Yeah, that's on Mondays. Tuesday it rotates. Chicken, broccoli and almonds.
早餐午餐晚餐都吃@些
For breakfast, lunch and dinner?
你想你鹤右惶烊餐吃一拥氖澄
You want our son to eat the same thing three times a day?
消化系yγ庖呦到y能造成很大影
Eighty percent of our immune system starts in the gut.
吃的食物我恍 就能L
Keep it simple in the gut, you get to live a long life.
你要他@N吃一周 他就自⒘
A week on this diet and he'll wanna kill himself.
我@是送他上^路
And I'll help him do it.
我告V你 你ξ倚迅屑
You know what, you should be grateful.
我爸爸早餐吃半西柚 三杯小可
My dad started my day with half a grapefruit and three lines of primo coke.
他f@就是最美妙的早餐
"Breakfast of champions," he called it.
所以你鹤蝇F在B巧克力糖棒都不能吃了
And now your son can't look at a candy bar without breaking into hives.
那真是恭喜你打破了盒匝h啊
Congratulations, you've broken the cycle.
我以前X得
And to think...
我U喜g你@嘴的
I used to love the mouth on you.
我在跟律贤
I've spoken to my lawyer.
我想重新安排一下 我他十天 你他四天
We want a new arrangement. Ten days with me, four with you.
嗯
Huh.
我的安排是 我他十四天 你Lhc
Here's my counter offer. Fourteen days with me and none with you.
你X得你的律怎N看
Let's see what your lawyer thinks about that.
- 早上好 阿雅 - 早上好 野R
- Morning, Aya. - Hey, Mustang.
有消息f林博失了
They say Limbo's disappeared.
e心 他恢驼常的
Don't worry about it, he'll get over it.
@是莫扎特的曲子N
Is that Mozart?
巴赫的 巴赫的曲子很好分辨 因樗真的很有l理
Bach. You can always tell Bach because he's really mathematical.
- 他是不是那喜gШ⒆拥囊芳 - 是啊
- Is he the one with all the kids? - Yeah, 20.
很y想像他居然有精力去作曲
It's a wonder he found any time to compose.
足球下注的事 我想你臀
I need your help with my fantasy football.
我一龆稼A不了
I can't... I can't win a game.
@是想AX
Playing for money?
然是想AX
Yeah, of course I'm playing for money.
你o克利夫m布朗下了四注
You got four Cleveland Browns on your team.
竟是我主鲫
Well, they're my home team.
做人就是要忠\嘛
What's a man without loyalty?
我筒涣四
I can't help you.
你好 路口太窄 ^不去了
Hey, there's not enough room to pass,
我在想你能不能倒回岔道重新清咭幌铝硪l路
I was wondering if you'd back down to the turnoff?
可以
Any chance you could back up?
@事只有你知我知吧
Um, just between you and me, right?
天知地知 你知我知
Me, you and frosty.
好的
Sure.
你根本不知道你@是惹上了什N人
You have no clue who you're messing with, man.
我惹上了什N人
Who am I messing with?
你完蛋了 夥
You're dust, pal.
告V我
Tell me.
你在浪Mrg
You're wasting your time.
老^子 你累了N
Are you tired, old man?
嗯
Yeah.
芊颉た搜Y斯滕森 「杉塔」
格蕾z
Grace?
你磉@质颤N
What are you doing here?
P死了
Kyle's dead.
有人⒑α怂
Somebody killed him.
那跟我有什NPS
What's that got to do with me?
我能M屋N
Can I come in?
你最好把鞋子了再M屋 要不然她就δ悴豢饬
Better take your shoes off. She'll skin you alive.
我去打
I'm going to make some phone calls.
查一下P究竟是出了什N事
Find out what happened to Kyle.
她以槟闶堑郎系娜
She thinks you're one of the guys from the old days.
e管她了
Don't worry about her.
^mfP的事 他跟一叫但丁的小混混走的比^近
Kyle. He got mixed up with some clown by the name of Dante.
他偷了一千克可卡因 那是S京的
And they stole a kilo of coke from Viking.
- S京是l - 他是一位大毒n
- Who's Viking? - Drug dealer. A big one.
- 你JR他 - 他是流鼻涕的小屁孩的r候我就JR他了
- You know him? - Yeah, when he was a snot-nosed kid.
- 我JR他爸 布利特 - 爸也JR@布利特
- I knew his old man, Bullitt. - Dad knew him, too?
布利特要做什N大Q定的r候 就碚椅野 後砦野植至 就碚椅
Whenever Bullitt had rough stuff to be done, that was his go-to guy. After Dad, me.
然後@S京接手了
And then Viking took over.
@S京行事L格跟他爸截然不同
Viking's a whole different breed.
他喜g出手人
He likes hurting people.
我要⒘怂 布_克
I'm gonna kill him, Brock.
嗯
Sure you are.
你怎N知道你能下手⑷
What makes you think you can kill a man?
我
I've...
我已⒘怂的三手下
I've killed three of his guys.
你怎N理企w的
What did you do with the bodies?
用FzW捆好 然後扔到{谷Y去
Wrapped them in chicken wire, threw them on the gorge.
- 用FzW - 然後有~把企w吃掉
- Chicken wire? - Yeah, to let the fish get at them.
它能把肉都吃掉
They'll eat the flesh off the bones.
@企w就不上浮 就能解Q泼
So the bodies don't fill with gas and rise.
然後浮到水面上的}了
They stay at the bottom.
- 你是哪W到@一招的 - 我是在一本犯罪小fYW到的
- Where did you learn that? - I read it in a crime novel.
- 他是我兄弟 - 兄弟
- He is my brother. - Brother?
扯淡
My ass.
我知道
I know.
- 也S你可以... - ]嘴
- Maybe I should... - Shut up.
e惹麻
You stay out of trouble.
榱矍榘
The things we do for love, huh?
她在妓院收yT的r候 手垦蛄艘恍┝沐X
She was skimming the till at a massage parlor.
他lF了 我去揍她一D 然而...
They sent me to beat the shit out of her. Instead...
格蕾z怎N恿
How's Grace?
她走了
She left.
我得f 她走的真是r候
The lady's got good timing, I'll give her that.
我要怎N才能找到@叫「S京」的砘
How do I find this Viking?
你找不到的
You don't.
- 你最多也只能值小D - 我再想ck法
- You've gone as far up the ladder as you're gonna go. - We'll see.
一人失]什N 人失那就不正常了
One guy can disappear. Two? I don't think so.
三人失了 有那些不翼而w
Three? With ten keys of coke?
也S他是一夥的
Maybe they were all in it together.
你X得我有三手下_溜了
You think three of my dealers ran out on me?
我B自己的手下都不t解 我就成了咱@最大的糊T蛋了 @就是你的推
That would make me the worst judge of character in the Rockies, that's your theory?
- 不是 - 嗯
- No. - No.
肯定是那些愚蠢的印第安人值
It was those goddamn Indians.
我的父H想跟他合作 真是犯了大e
This is all my father's fault for getting into bed with them.
抱歉 你f什N印第安人
I'm sorry, the Indians?
最_始S京他父H在道上混的r候
When Viking's father was first getting started,
他跟一叫烟夭的印第安人做了一P交易
he made a deal with an Indian named White Bull.
他o@烟夭供 烟夭在保o^u
He supplied him, White Bull dealt on the reservation.
直到烟夭想要U大自己的地P
Until White Bull wanted more turf.
- 所以他把一些偏h的破落子o了烟夭 - 比如基W市@拥
- So he tossed White Bull a few piece of crap towns. - Like Kehoe.
後砘W打造成了一座滑雪度假俚 Χ酒沸枨罅看笤
And Kehoe builds a ski resort. Turns it into a gold mine.
v史教我很重要的一c
What's the one thing history's taught us?
那就是要那些印第安人e出保留^
You keep those Indians on the reservation.
那些印第安人是j求不M
Those Indians, they're always wanting more.
因樗X得@些地P本砭投际撬的
Because they think the turf was theirs all along.
倒是有追值览
Might kinda have a point there, right.
他_成交易的r候
White Bull gave this to my father...
烟夭把@玩意o了我父H
the day they shook on their deal.
嗯
Yeah.
是r候把@玩意送回去了
It's time we give it back to him.
- 有什N需要我椭的 - 你可以坐下o我v故事
- What can I do for you two? - You could sit down with us. Tell us your story.
- F在客人很多 我很忙 - F在我眼Y只有你一位
- I got other customers. - Yeah, that's funny. All I can see in here is you.
能不能告V我你哪天上晚班
Please tell me you work nights.
L四 槭颤N@
Thursdays. Why?
白天看你如此美 想看看晚上看你是什N效果
You look this good in sunlight, I gotta see you after dark.
我要一份u蛋培根煎
Eggs, bacon, pancakes.
你呢
And for you?
你硖舭
Surprise me.
好的
Okay.
我13q那年 我爸RKr 跟我f
I was 13 when my dad kicked it. You know his last words to me?
你要想k法把餐^Y槲曳者^的服T都o睡了
"Try to bang every waitress who ever serves you."
基WC
那印第安佬怎N不
This Indian is taking forever to show up.
跟我ff你睡e^服T的小把虬
So, tell me about this motel trick of yours.
付我二十K就v
Twenty bucks.
@不是什N小把
It's not a trick, all right.
我@套路害O了 B史蒂夫・滩妓苟KKQ奇
It's a beautiful invention. It's an invention Steve Jobs would have been proud of.
- 史蒂夫・滩妓 -
- Steve Jobs, huh? - That's right.
是什N他成橐晃惶觳 那就是|
You know what made that guy such a genius? Simplicity.
- 你直f吧 - 好的
- Let's hear it already. - All right.
我平均一年在e^住100晚上
I stay in motels 100 nights a year, right.
每天早上 我F在T上煲K需要打叩呐谱
First thing, every morning, I hang a "clean the room" sign on the doorknob.
e^服T看到牌子 就推_T
Maid sees the sign, she opens the door.
注意接下淼
Now, pay attention to the details here.
都是精心安排好的
All the hard thought behind them.
我全裸躺在床上
I'm lying on top of the covers, stone naked.
最重要的一c是 你要直e^女W的眼睛
First crucial part, I look into the maid's eyes, all right?
如果不直她的眼睛 她就直接溜了 那就全完了
If I don't, she backs right outta that door. It's over before it even starts.
我拿上@20K 放到我u荷
I take the twenty, I lay it right on my Jimmy.
- 就行了 - 20美元就螯N
- Boom. - Just a twenty?
那些e^服T每小r只八K三毛五 她日子也不容易
Maids make $8.35 an hour, and they've got miserable lives too.
^得不怎N
That's the totally underrated part of this.
所以@完全由她Q定
The ball is completely in her court.
她可以走出房g 什N}都]有
She could back out of that door no harm, no foul.
或者她可以^砟眠@X
Or... she could come and get it.
- 你的成功率有多少 - 百分之31
- What's your success rate? - Thirty-one percent.
一年住100晚上 所以我很S富
Hundred motels a year, you do the math.
他跟烟夭一右泊髂欠NS色的手套
He's got the same little yellow gloves White Bull wears.
- 印第安人都@ - 估是吧
- Is that an Indian thing? - I guess.
很好
It's good.
真是好O了
That's Steve fucking Jobs good.
有} @ο蟮馁|量你控制不好啊
I see one flaw. Quality control.
我才付了20K 能睡到多漂亮的
I'm paying her 20 bucks, I'm not asking for Miss America.
估全也]有31值得我睡的漂亮服T啊
Still, there's no way there's 31 maids in the whole country worth banging.
看 你感到@的
You'd be surprised.
我的天
Oh dear.
了一晚上了 ]出什N
Been at it all night, haven't gotten a thing out of him.
你然不出
And you won't.
你懂什N叫疼痛吧
You know, pain...
他早就T了
it's like a religion to these guys.
我跟你f @些阿帕奇印第安人 以前X得受到折磨是一Ns耀
You know, the Apaches used to consider getting tortured a mark of honor.
@r值^真是可怕
How's that for a value system?
他是q特印第安人
He's a Ute.
- 怎Nf - @周的都是印第安人q特人 不是阿帕奇印第安人
- What now? - Local Indians are Utes. Not Apache.
我的前妻可是印第安人 你X得我分不清
You know I married an Indian. Don't you think I know the difference?
西蒙・R格 「r」
以前基W市]出^@拥陌缸
This doesn't happen in Kehoe.
F在出了
It just did.
他第一次去就出事了
It was his first run.
他跟我f 父H 就去一次
"Just one run, Papa," he says to me.
我能行的
"I can do it."
我可是你的鹤
"I'm your son."
我要怎Nk
What are we going to do?
我回家 去丹佛
Okay, let's go home to Denver.
考曼先生
Mr. Coxman.
您的鹤尤ナ 我很y^
I'm very sorry for your loss.
xxP心
Thanks.
那
So...
- o你 - xx
- Here you go. - Thanks.
我前男朋友F在在丹佛的毒分局工作 我今天o他打了
Ex-boyfriend of mine works Vice in Denver. So I gave him a call today.
因槟阆胨 想他^的怎N
Because you missed him and wanted to see how he was doing.
@嘛 他X得我z有
Well, he still thinks there's a chance for us.
他叫什N名字
What's his name?
柯特
Kurt.
- 你z了多久 - 我的天 月
- How long were you two lovers? - Oh, Jesus. Two months, okay.
我看了煸诼放粕夏俏坏尿蟾 死者叫西蒙・立格
I had him look up the forensics on our sign hanger. The guy's name is Simon LeGrew.
他的父H是烟夭
Now, his father is White Bull.
一位印第安毒^目 碜缘し
He's a Native American drug dealer from Denver
在@附近N毒品已有三十多年
who's been dealing coke around here for 30 years.
烟夭和「S京」的萘是重B的
So now, White Bull shares territory with Viking.
「S京」是另一位毒^目 真名特雷弗・卡柯
He's a Denver drug dealer whose real name is Trevor Calcote.
所以
So...
我X得
I'm thinking...
F在他在Z地P
what we have here is a turf war.
毒集F之g的Y
A drug turf war.
就在咱基W市M行
Right here in Kehoe.
所以我F在要怎N
So what are we gonna do about it?
根我木30多年淼慕 @案子w丹佛毒部T管
Well, my 30 years' experience tells me that this is a job for Denver Vice.
我打一通5分的 所t解到地毒n的情r 比你^去三十年
It doesn't bother you that I just learned more about a local drug lord
掌握的情r都多 y道@都]有|幽泓N
in five minutes on the phone than you've learned in 30 years?
能|游业氖 柯特躺在床上 f一番 就把你忽悠住了
What bothers me is that Kurt's lying in bed tonight convinced that he's back in your heart.
柯特可不是小孩子
Kurt's a big boy.
我知道你回
I knew you'd be back.
好吧 我告V你 S京的真名是特雷弗・卡柯
All right, Viking's real name is Trevor Calcote.
如果你要取他性命 就得雇位⑹
If you want him dead, you're gonna have to hire a hit man.
- ⑹贮N - 就是刺客
- A hit man? - Yeah. An assassin.
你知道怎N能雇到一位⑹贮N
Do you know one?
知道 他b是「鬯够摩人」
The Eskimo.
那我具w要怎N操作
So, how does this work?
你o「鬯够摩人」I一火票 他害怕坐wC
You buy The Eskimo a train ticket. He's afraid to fly.
去火站接他 然後送他去旅^
You pick him up at the train station, you drive him to a motel
付他一半定金
where you give him half the money upfront.
然後你回家
And then you go home.
- 然後我要怎N知道事情k妥了 - 你看丹佛]缶托辛
- How do I know when it's done? - Keep checking The Denver Post.
死了@N人肯定大肆蟮
They can't resist a good rub out.
他取@N多b是什N意思 斯皮多 S京 鬯够摩
What is it with all these nicknames? Speedo, Viking, Eskimo.
道上的人都@
The Eskimo. It's a gangster thing.
那你有bN
Did you have a nickname?
「僚C」
Yeah. Wingman.
Wingman?
出是《阎玖桦》 「你可以我的僚C」
Yeah, from Top Gun. As in "you can be my Wingman."
「僚C」
Wingman.
c著啊
Come on.
我^了 夥
I tried, buddy.
麻Q首歌
Some real music, please.
- 你想什N - 只要不坎耶的就行
- What do you want to hear? - Anything else. Just no Kanye.
e付他小M了
Take it out of his tip.
因槌茄YF在在ek一h @是我能租到的最好的房g了
There's a convention in town. This is all I could get.
- @Y只有我_r的一半 - ]e
- This is only half. - That's right.
你是l子N
Are you a cop?
不是
No.
槭颤N我@N是因l子的P底是跟不上r代
The reason I ask is cops are always a year behind the street.
道上的人都知道是要先付三分之二 事成之後再付三分之一
But the street knows it's two-thirds upfront, one-third when the deal is done.
l子F在以槭窍阮A付一半 事成後再付另一半
But cops... they still think it's half and half.
好吧 我o你三分之二的定金
Okay. We can do two-thirds.
我把事情k妥的
We're gonna get along just fine.
值钠亮
Yes!
值钠亮 到一fK了
Yes! Ten grand! Ten grand, baby!
一fK了
Ten grand!
攻方持球越得分了 你的主了 你不是f要忠\
That Jet touchdown just beat your Browns. Whatever happened to loyalty?
有r候忠\是要付出代r的
Sometimes loyalty comes at a price.
而且我奶奶是布克林人
And besides, my grandmother's from Brooklyn.
那你到的X是不是要分她一c
So? Why don't you give her a cut?
什N事
Yeah?
鬯够摩砹 他f他手上有你感d趣的情
Says he's The Eskimo. Says he has information you wanna buy.
f砺
Let's hear him out.
有人出九fK 我值裟
I've been offered ninety grand to ice you.
值粑
To ice me?
想⑷ 去找「鬯够摩人」 我f^的
You wanna ice a guy, you go to The Eskimo. Well, that works for me.
烟夭居然出得起@N「多」X
Who knew White Bull had that kind of coin?
烟夭是印第安人 他想⑷丝刹外包出去
White Bull's an Indian. Indians don't farm out their kills.
- 所以幕後黑手不是烟夭 那是l - 我就是碣u@l情蟮
- So, if it wasn't White Bull, then who the hell was it? - That's what I'm selling.
- 你出r多少 - 9fK
- Well, how much? - Ninety grand.
你算P打得很精啊
You gotta love the symmetry, there.
你真是位精明的商人
You are one hell of a businessman.
我意向如此
I tries.
一向如此 不是意向如此
Try. It's a singular.
- 你X得咱@P交易做得成N - 然可以
- Do we have a deal? - 'Course we got a deal.
把X打到@_曼群u的y行~上
Deposit the money into this Cayman Islands account.
X到~ 我就告V你那人的名字
When it hits, you get the name.
很好
Goody.
我就喜g跟懂行的人打交道
I like working with pros.
省掉那些U
Cuts way down on the bullshit factor.
好的 那N
Yeah. So...
l想要我的命
who wants me dead?
那人叫考曼
Guy's name is Coxman.
考曼?
Coxman.
原砦腋赣H的手下有叫考曼的
There was a Coxman on Dad's payroll, right?
那砘锝惺颤N碇 他的b
What was his name? He called himself, uh, Wing... Ding...
是「僚」什N碇
Ringworm... Wing... Ding...
- 僚C - 僚C
- Wingman. - Wingman!
僚C
Wingman!
@叫「僚C」的砘锵胍我的命 槭颤N
Wingman wants me dead? Why?
那不P我的事 我牟贿^@些
The why of it ain't my business so I don't aks.
- 那你去他 - 我的事已k完了
- Ask. - I think our business here is done.
嗯
So it is.
能不能我再}
Hey, can I ask two questions? If I may.
一私人}加一I的}
One pro to another.
吧
Shoot.
他槭颤No你起「鬯够摩」@N一b
Why do they call you The Eskimo?
那是住我家居的兄弟o我取的
Comes from the brothers in the hood.
要是哪黑人敢搬到K日下雪的地方住 那他的肯定是鬯够摩人
Any nigga crazy enough to move up to snow country has gotta be a fucking Eskimo.
你真有意思
That's... you're funny.
另一}呢
- Second question. - All right, it's...
y道]有人教^你道上的矩N
Who taught you your ethics?
你再f一遍
Come again?
人家出九fK雇你⑽ 而你s]有遵守s定
You made a deal to kill me for 90 grand and you didn't honor that deal.
因槲以谧袷睾湍愕募s定
It's because I'm honoring this one.
嗯
Yeah.
那你在道上 就算不上一言九鼎啊
Guess a man's word doesn't matter in the hood, right?
人在江湖都是榱俗约喊
Guess it's just every man for himself in there.
你知道在道上混 人品是很重要的
You see, out here, character counts.
要是人品不行 就不成生意
Without character there can be no business and...
要是生意不成
without business...
那
well...
那如何是好呢
what the hell would we do all day?
衢T影字幕g迎P注微博 @hb字幕Mv
字幕M官方公：禾影
若是想施展您的翻g才A 自己的名字出F在字幕_^
hb字幕Mg迎您加入
hb字幕M招新群 483552098
招募英翻 校εc特效人T \邀您的加入
能不能不要踩在地毯上
Would you mind stepping off the rug?
RD・蒂德 「鬯够摩」
@就是所^的「鬯够摩翻L」
Is this what you call an Eskimo Roll?
我在考]去m
I'm thinking Ireland.
或者去德
Maybe Germany.
去质颤N呢
Yeah? For what?
花一fK度假
- My ten grand vacation. - Oh.
mU不e的
Yeah, well, Guinness over Becks any day.
去都柏林吧
Then Dublin it is.
你要我去都柏林
You're gonna take me to Dublin?
野R 如果他lF我了
Mustang, if we get caught out.
查找 特雷弗・卡柯 丹佛]
丹佛花花公子的生日狂g 我喜g紊
「僚C」
Wingman.
近砣绾
How the hell you been?
上跟我出去兜兜L吧
We'd like you to come for a little ride.
跟我「鬯够摩」的事吧
Okay, Wingman, tell me about The Eskimo.
我想你花X]殖墒掳
I guess you just don't get what you pay for anymore.
- 是有人殖闪说 - 是N
- Some of us do. - Oh yeah?
那斯皮多 林博 有杉塔呢
Well, what about Speedo and Limbo and Santa?
那些人怎N恿
How did those guys work out for you, huh?
在我值裟阒前 我有件事想你 你槭颤N要那N做
Okay. Now before you die, you're gonna tell me what this is all about.
你能承受多大的痛苦
The only question is, how much pain do you wanna endure?
我反正也活不L了 去你的那些酷刑吧
I got cancer of the ass, dickweed. So screw you, and screw your pain.
你想知道F在究竟是什N情r
You wanna know what this is all about?
- 一切都因布利特而起 - 因槲野
- It's about Bullitt. - My father?
那混蛋睡了我女人
Lying piece of shit stole my woman.
我爸是女的就能睡
Dad banged anything with a hole.
骨^ 以前道上是怎Nf他的
Hey Bone, what is it you used to say about him?
要是有人抓著尾蛇的^ 我爸都敢掏出攀挪
He'd bang a rattlesnake if someone held its head.
- o意冒犯 - ]事
- No offense. - No, none taken.
- 我爸睡^的女人刀挡磺 - 可其中有一位是我的女人
- Dad had thousands of women. - Yeah, well, one of them was mine.
- 他的事跟我有什NPS - 因槟闶撬鹤
- What's that got to do with me? - His rancid blood runs through your veins.
他那愚蠢的L相 跟你如出一H
And that stupid grin of his is plastered all over your arrogant face.
我的在哪
Where's my cocaine?
我_所Y了
I flushed it down the toilet.
- 那可有10千克啊 - 至少10千克吧
- That was ten kilos. - At least.
f老 我以椴恢鼓屈Nc呢
Honestly, I thought it was more.
你⑽沂窒 偷我的
So, you kill my men,
就因樗的一女人
you steal my coke, over a goddamn woman?
@就叫矍 小伙子 你去垡人是什N感X
It's called love, sweetheart. You should try it sometime.
我完了N
Now, are we done?
是你想^m扯淡 小子
Or do you want to keep on chatting, skippy?
好啊 「僚C」
Okay, Wingman.
你真行啊 夥
See, that's how you do it, fellas.
y怪你@N牛
That's how you go out strong.
布洛克・考曼 「僚C」
@Y是基W市警局
Kehoe Precinct.
- 好的 稍等 金 - 什N事
- Yeah, just a sec. Kim. - Yeah?
丹佛毒部T的那位夥打淼
Denver Vice.
你好 柯特
Kurt, hi.
我深入{查了烟夭和S京的PS
So, that deep dive into Viking and White Bull that you asked for...
查了一些老n案
I got all the files here.
你最害了
You're the best.
可麻┝
Wasn't easy.
xx 你能直接通^]件把文件lo我
Thank you. Can you email them over?
可以是可以 我也可以_H自把文件送到你手上
I could. Or I could drive them up and put them right into your warm hands.
程三小r 所以我今晚要住在你那了
'Course, it's a three-hour drive, so I need a place to stay the night.
_可以 但情r是@
Well, there's always my place. But, here's the thing.
我今天一整晚上都要x那些文件
I really need to spend all night with those files.
F在不如你直接把文件lo我
Now, if you were to shoot them right over to me,
也S我今晚前就能x完
I could probably be done with them by tonight.
然後我就有精力去做e的事了
And then I could put all my pent up energy into something else.
好的 lo你吧
Hmm. Okay, well, you got them, baby. Bang.
你要的Y料都l到你]箱了
Right in your inbox.
好的 都收到了
Oh, they're right in there.
那我今晚怎N面
So, how do we wanna do this?
到r候晚上你ePT P艟托
I'm thinking you leave the door open and your lights off.
我能找到...
Trust me to find...
等一下 @是什N情r
Hold on a second. What was that?
我的天 我@l生雪崩了
- I said... - Oh God, we got an avalanche.
我待回o你
I gotta call you back.
好了 吉布
Oh, hey, Gip?
真棒
Yes!
我看起硐流浪h
Do I look like a homeless guy to you?
三十年前
Thirty years ago...
我住在一g房子的地下室Y 那房主是一位毒
I lived in a hole in the ground below the house of the guy that dealt me drugs.
有一天 他碚椅 他伸出手
One day, he came to me, stuck out his hand.
我握住了他的手
I took it.
我做了P交易
And we made a deal.
那交易不e
It was a good deal.
不算非常不e
Not a great deal.
我拿那PX和我兄弟I一座
I should have bought a casino like my brother.
但是_成的s定不能`背
But a deal is a deal.
我遵守了s定
And I honored it.
我遵守s定
That honor...
然而sK遭毒手
was repaid with butchery.
我的生子不幸拭
They took my only son.
今天
Today...
我要送我鹤踊丶
my boy will make his final journey home.
我留下
We will stay.
展_
Take our revenge.
以眼眼
I will have blood for blood.
他⑽鹤 我就⑺鹤
A son for a son.
嗨
Hi.
- 你忘了 - 的
- Goddamn it. - You forgot.
什N
What?
- 什N - 校@}的家L
- What? - The bullying seminar.
我的天
Oh, God.
- 孩子的父母都要到 - 你f得 我忘了要_了
- Every other parent was there. - You're right, I forgot about the bullying seminar.
但我忘了也]啥大不了的
But I'm allowed to forget, you know why?
我掏XoW校置了一新的算C中心
Because I wrote a check for a new computer center.
你付得起X 状渭议L]什N大不了的 世道就是如此
You write a check, you get to skip on 150 bullying seminars. That's the math.
@就是治疫@行能得到的好之一
That's one of the perks of my business.
特雷弗 你不是商人 你是罪犯
You're not a businessman, Trevor. You're a criminal.
我手上的已o法你M足了 我得r你可是非常M足
My powder's not good enough for you anymore? I remember when it was plenty good enough.
享受著那些粉末
When you used to roll around in it.
我得以前 你吸一c
See, I remember when just a little bit of my powder...
就能d^的跟匹野R似的
made you buck like a bronco.
的
Goddamn.
你@ζ亮的棕色眼睛 ]上吧
Close those beautiful brown eyes of yours.
想像那鼍鞍
See if it all comes back to you.
下周W校的募捐活有枰一位主持人 我o你竺了
They needed a host for next week's fundraiser. I signed you up.
我鹤邮锹}菲利普W校的秀W生
拿著
Here.
^去的一周 「S京」手下有三位毒失了
Three of Viking's drug dealers have disappeared in the last week.
那S京究竟是什N人碇 再告V我一遍
Tell me who Viking is again?
丹佛的毒n 烟夭的κ
The Denver drug lord. White Bull's rival.
我你}
Let me ask you a question.
我能拿@S京和@烟夭怎N幽
What is it you think we might do to Viking or to White Bull?
我可以除掉他 So城市治安
Take them out. Save our town.
我要解Q一小}
We got a little problem to solve.
我
We...
我之前把那印第安人的企w煸诼放粕 其@人是o辜的
we hung an innocent Indian from a road sign.
我X得烟夭恐怕有些不M
And my guess is White Bull's not gonna like that.
各位有]有什N挽回@稣`的k法
So, has anyone got any ideas on how we might set things right?
也S我去道歉
Yeah, maybe we should apologize.
怎Nf
Yeah?
我犯了小e` ]必要因此翻 我便lo他
One little screw up shouldn't make us their bitches. So we send them a short note.
@便l的热怎N呢
Hey, and what does this, uh, short note say?
我也不知道 比如f 之前那拥谋〔再l生了 怎N
I don't know. How about, "Sorry about Tonto, won't happen again"?
不好
No.
我X得我提供一些更有r值的|西 能表_我\意的|西
I'm thinking we need something with a bit more oomph. Something from our heart.
把他的^砍下 放到一盒子Y 送o他
Yeah, cut off his head. Stick it in a box and send it to them.
就f是他值
Tell them he's the culprit.
跟他f 我以前的s定可以照常M行
Tell them our old arrangement's back in effect and good to go.
把那玩意拿_ 夥
Get that shit away from me, man.
你是不是X子有}
What the hell's wrong with you?
我手上的大麻全世界都排的上 而且都是合法的
We've got some of the best pot stores in the world, man. All legal.
而你sx癯楸Ｗo^a的劣|土
But no, instead you choose to smoke that dang reservation weed.
也S我就好@口
Maybe I like it better.
@些白人
- White people, man. - Yeah.
我B^一b老鼠 都比@狗^要大
You know I had a rat that was bigger than that thing.
你著QQ口味
You should try smoking that shit instead.
真f心
That's gross.
Mom!
@周跟住 下周跟爸爸住
She gets him this week, father gets him next week.
你敢信 B孩子都要著
Can you imagine sharing your own son?
我的天
Damn.
- @Y是基W警局 - 我是柯特
- Kehoe. - Hey, it's Kurt.
你好 柯特
Hi, Kurt.
你配不上我提供的情
You don't deserve this intel.
- 什N情r - 先f 你配不上我提供的情
- Intel? - First tell me you don't deserve it.
我配不上你 你手上有什N情
I don't deserve it. What you got?
lF了一具企w 死者是但丁・菲斯特 基W市人 企w是在丹佛附近一山谷YlF的
A body. Dante Ferstel. Kehoe kid. Found dead in a Denver alley.
但丁・菲斯特
死於吸毒^量 也]什N新r的
Smack overdose. So, what's new, right?
又是一位L末吸毒吸太嗨的人呀
Just another Saturday night sleeper.
但是PI在於 @但丁是C鲐\毒品的一小D
And here's the kicker. Dante was a baggage monkey at the airport.
你是f基W市C
The Kehoe airport?
考曼先生
Mr. Coxman.
有何F
What can I do for you?
P於您鹤佑幸恍┣r 我想聿t解一下
It's about your son.
- 我不知道你J不JR但丁・菲斯特 - 他死於吸毒^量
- I didn't know if you'd heard about Dante Ferstel. - Yeah. He died of an overdose.
但丁和你的鹤佣荚C錾习
Dante worked with your son at the airport, right?
- Π - 你JR他
- Yeah. - Did you know him?
不
No.
P]跟你提起^他
Kyle never mention him to you?
]有
No.
就是@的
Is that it?
就@些了
I guess it is.
我不明白你槭颤N跑砀我f@些
I don't understand why you're here.
想查清真相
Truth?
我X得你的鹤硬皇前a君子
I don't think your son was a junkie.
我X得但丁・菲斯特也不是a君子
And I don't think Dante Ferstel was either.
那你X得他@是什N情r
So, what do you think happened to them?
我目前不清晰
I don't know.
我希望你能o我提供一些有用的信息
I was hoping you might be able to tell me something that could help.
抱歉
Sorry...
我筒涣四
I can't help you.
你也筒涣宋 我有活要干
You can't help me. I got work to do.
我明白
I understand.
z
Tape.
Taser.
有抗生素
Antibiotics.
槭颤NЭ股素
Antibiotics?
你]被小孩子咬^吧
Yeah, you ever been bitten by a kid?
@些小孩子可害了 要是他咬你一口 可比被狗咬了遭
Little bastards are nasty. You almost wish you were bitten by a dog.
什N事
Yes?
好的
Okay.
我F在不能邮
We can't grab him yet.
- 槭颤N - 他派了位信使
- Why not? - They're sending a messenger.
我就是信使
I am the messenger.
感x您接我
Thank you for seeing me.
@砘锓赶碌盒 我已他命了 我想恢秃推
He's been punished for his deed. We want peace with you again.
好的
Okay.
很感x你送淼亩Y物
I appreciate the gift.
你很wN
It was thoughtful.
你敢一人磉@ 是很有N的
You showed a lot of guts coming here alone.
但是他⒘宋鹤 我就要⑺鹤
But I need a son for a son.
加勒姆・M南多 「滑^」
小心c 要不然打附近的孩子
Careful, man! You might hit a kid.
你再y 我就⒘四
If you do it again, I'll kill you.
什N事
Yes?
- 各位明天 - 再
- See you guys tomorrow. - Hey, Ryan.
今天我接你回去
Um, I'm taking you home today.
但@周我要去和我住
But this is my mom's week to pick me up.
我知道 她目前在牙t那 她我斫幽
Yeah, I know, but she got stuck at the dentist. Asked me to come and get you.
怎N了
What?
我湫影
We take him.
- 他派淼男攀乖觞N恿 - ⒘
- What about the messenger? - We shot the messenger.
我不得她跟我f^她去看牙t了啊
I don't remember her telling me about a trip to the dentist.
她牙根管出了c}
Yeah, she had a root canal develop some problems.
你爸爸我斫幽
And your dad said could I pick you up. So, here I am.
- 我坐@v - 原砟禽v特斯拉呢
- This is us here. - What happened to the Tesla?
的
Shit!
M好安全
Seatbelt.
- 他鹤釉谀 - 他上了一v小溜了
- Where's the kid? - He got away in a van.
什N拥男∝
What kind of a van?
上面有「基W市」字
Said "Kehoe" on it.
我找到那孩子 我找到那v 很快的
We'll find the kid. We'll find the van. It won't take us long.
把@企w和@人^理掉 要不然就要l臭了
Get rid of these two before they start to stink.
接
Answer the phone.
你好
Hello?
不 他F在接不了你的
No, he can't talk right now.
因樗已死了
Because he's dead.
我走 坐三v
Let's go. Three cars.
那企w怎Nk
What about the body?
米妮I 你斫Q
Minya, take care of this.
我很忙 叫他的印第安人去解Q啊
I'm busy. Let the fucking Indian do it.
你不是我爸爸的手下吧
You don't work for my father, do you?
那些追我的人是l
Who were those guys anyways?
不知道
I don't know.
不用管他
You don't have to worry about them.
好吧
Right.
他要是抓了我鹤 不可能不打^
They can't take my son and not call.
不是@拥
That's not how it's done.
@些印第安鬼佬
Those tepee asswipes.
Those goddamn alkies.
我要把他都值 然後把他的企w煸倪@到q他州的每一K路牌上
I'm gonna take one of them, I'm gonna hang them from every road sign from here to Utah.
要是架了e人的孩子 就o他家L打 大家都知道@c
You take a man's son, you call! Everybody knows that!
他架了我的孩子
I mean, they took my boy.
我的孩子
My little boy.
你了 @周我Ш⒆
Are you insane! This is my week.
你不跟我打招呼就去接孩子 你自己的鹤佣冀架 你是不是太蠢了
You pick him up without asking? Are you so damn stupid you'd kidnap your own son?
我真是迫不及待想律把新的狃Bfh好了 狃B嗳o我
I can't wait to watch my lawyer write up the new arrangement. Full custody.
你一月能他小r就算不e了
You'll be lucky to get him two hours a month. Two supervised hours.
警察在F隹粗你 跟他共小r
A cop in the room with you, watching you play.
在他高中I前 你就e想著跟他为面了
You won't get him alone until he graduates from high school.
也不用绦心隳怯薮赖娘食了
A public high school! With normal kids. And no stupid diets!
我X得你不敢再ξ邮幽_了
I guess you won't be doing that again.
Π
Right? Uh-huh.
不在那
He's not here.
什N
- What? - Ah...
把歌P了
Turn that song off.
牧硪手Cl淼亩绦
It's a text. From a different number.
t杉e^ 12房
"Sequoia Motel. Room twelve."
史蒂夫・滩妓
"Steve Jobs, baby."
打叻块g xx
的
Hello.
做成づ竦男
A little peepee tepee.
的
Oh, shit.
安|・迪克 「骨^」
我懂@行的矩 他提要求 我M足他的要求
I know how this world works. They call with their demands. I give them what they want.
他就把鹤铀突
We get Ryan back.
一天纫不到我鹤 我就缶
In 24 hours, I call the police.
我一天染湍茏他平安回家
In 24 hours, he'll be home.
- 你在地zY活活死 - 是啊
- You'll burn in hell for this. - Yeah.
咱地zY
I'll see you there.
g迎光R基W蒙特克R酒店
Welcome to Kehoe Chateau Montclair.
- 我今晚需要房g - 抱歉 需要提前A定
- We need rooms tonight. - I'm sorry, you need a reservation.
抱歉 你f什N
Excuse me.
您A定了房g
A reservation.
你f什N
Really?
抱歉 我不是那意思
A reser... Oh! No, I didn't mean it like that.
我的意思是你提前A定房g
I meant you need to reserve... book before you get here
F在咱@都住M了 我@的入住流程就是@拥
because we're all full. That's all I meant.
我跟你f 我到的是
You know what I heard?
你叫我和我的朋友L回印第安人保o^
You told me and my friends that we need to go back to the reservation.
不
Oh, no.
你知不知道 我能把@l
Do you have any idea what I can do to you...
在cuW站上
on Yelp?
你要N叫你理^
You might wanna get your boss out here.
要N你看看@入住嘛 有]有e的k法
Or you could take another look.
我看看啊
I will take another look.
- 你I了 - 然
- You hungry? - Sure.
你吃煎蛋
Eggs?
嗯
Okay.
- 你住在@ - 嗯
- You live here? - Yeah.
你一人住
All alone?
嗯
Yeah.
你]有孩子
You don't have any kids?
]有
No.
你喜guL
You like rock?
我喜g古典音
I like classical.
你把我У侥慵已Y 可不是明智的做法
It wasn't very smart bringing me to your house.
怎N了
Why?
我想跟你父H
I want to talk to your dad.
今天晚上
Tonight?
明天早上
In the morning.
有c油
They're a bit greasy.
你f你]有孩子
You said you didn't have any kids.
他搬走了
He went away.
去床上睡吧
Go on, get in bed.
你在哪睡
Where are you gonna sleep?
大d那^的P室
In my room, down the hall.
- 要是我逃走了怎Nk - 你跑不了的 孩子
- What if I run away? - There's nowhere for you to go, kid.
外面天寒地 你出T就鏊懒 晚安
You'd freeze to death out there. Goodnight.
我睡前一般要故事
I always get read a story before bed.
- 我不v故事 - 你o我x什N都可以 我不在乎是什N热
- I don't know any stories. - You can read me anything. I don't care what it is.
@台新C-130P雪非常先M
The new C-130 is the creme de la crme of snow-pushers.
@一然大物重三
Built to humble Mother Nature, she has a rated load of three tons.
前置的P雪C器能m多N用途
The Overhausen UTV attachment snow blowers are made for universal use,
b溆大的lC
equipped with powerful modern engines.
除雪效率很高 m性
They're extremely effective and flexible.
每小r能理四千e雪
A capacity of four thousand tons of snow per hour.
⒌揭话儆⒊咧外
Throwing distance of a hundred feet.
@C器真不e
She is a great machine, all right.
我平r_的就是@
I've got one of these.
我以槟闶墙架犯
I thought you were a kidnapper.
我有e的身份啊
Not all the time.
那能不能我上去坐一回
Well, can I get a ride in it?
你去睡吧
You are going to sleep.
你有]有f^斯德哥摩C合征
Have you heard of the Stockholm Syndrome?
中u造
早上好 老
Morning, boss.
找到了
Did you find him?
]有 找到的
Not yet. We will.
烟夭先生
Mr. White Bull.
@Y送滑雪票 祝你L末玩的_心
These are some complimentary ski passes. Good for the whole weekend.
o您和您的朋友
For you and all of your... friends.
我想再次感xT位入住我酒店
And I just wanna thank you again for choosing to stay with us.
我知道你有e的安排
We know that you do have other entertainment options.
xx你
Thank you.
- @位布R恩在的那W校的Tl - Tl
- Janitor from Ryan's school. - Janitor, why not?
很s幸到您 我到一些消息
It's an honor to be here. You hear the whispers but...
- 你有什N想告V我的 - Φ
- You have something for me? - I might.
匪_的那v 我以前^
The van your boy got into. I've seen it before.
那司C我也^
And the guy that was driving that van, I've seen him too.
我和我家人去基W度假的r候
Me and my family go up to the resort in Kehoe.
- 你f^那家豪A的蒙克R酒店吧 - 嗯
- You know, the fancy one? Chateau Montclair. - Oh, yeah.
我_上山 打滑
Well, we're driving up and, you know, she scoots over and she's...
你的懂我的意思吧
showing a little appreciation on the way up, you get my drift?
嗯
- I do. - Yeah.
你有]有^ 不打滑
You ever tried to keep the wheel straight when someone's...
^mf那的事
The van.
^mf那v r那v停下 司C出手土宋
Well, like I was saying. The van that stopped to help me...
你鹤右簿褪巧狭四禽v
that's the same van that your boy got into.
那位出手臀野衍拉出涎Y的司C
And the guy who pulled me out of the ditch that night...
就是他抓走了你的孩子
he's the same guy that picked up your boy.
他的名字估你永生y忘
He's got one of those names that you never ever forget.
考曼
Coxman.
考曼?
我笑了一整晚上
Yeah. We laughed about it all night long.
- 因樗... - 我的天
- Because what she was doing... - Oh my God.
- 考曼有H戚 - 他]缶
- Coxman had a relative. - And he hasn't spoken with the cops.
我的手下出了多少r
Well... how much did my guy offer you?
一fK
Ten grand.
那就一fK吧
Ten grand it is.
w斯・沙洛姆  「Tl」
去看看他
Hey! Hey, check him out.
你了 雪崩
You're crazy, Avalanche!
你_定你以前]玩^@
You sure you've done this before?
小子 我生砭w
I was born to fly, white boy.
你鹤釉谖沂稚 你一人硪我 要不然我就⒘怂
I have your son. If you wanna see him alive, come alone.
我懂矩
Yeah, yeah. I know how it's done.
你想要多少X
So, how much do you want for him?
你到了我再 基W市考瑞路2210
We'll talk about that when you get here. 2210 Quarry Road. Kehoe.
我x_丹佛市 三小r後到基W市
I'm just leaving Denver. It's gonna take me about three hours.
基W市
我的天
Jesus Christ.
他的
Son of a...
警方
- 你好 - 你好 在休假
- Hey. - Hey. Taking a day off?
- 大路上又都是e雪啊 - 我一就去清
- Main road could use a plow. - I'll get to it soon.
我侄子砜次伊
My nephew. Visiting.
家人沓茄Y玩 很不e啊
Must be a comfort to have family in town.
我在路上看到很多都堵了
We saw all the cars at your place.
嗯
Yeah.
看@
Look at this.
- 所以我知道他在搞基 - 不是
- So now we know he's banging a hippie. - No.
公司的名字在卡上
On the truck. The company name.
- 路面清障公司 - x@4英里h
- Open Road. - It's four miles away.
- 集合出l - 出l
- Get the men. - Let's go.
- 真好玩 - 我要你
- That was so much fun! - I need you...
坐在@
to sit here...
等著e人斫幽
and wait till someone comes to get you.
- 他去路面清障公司的炝 - 再f一遍 你f什N
- They're headed to Open Road Garage. - Again. Say what?
路面清障公司的
Open Road Garage.
在W本路上
On Old Bend Road.
瑞恩
Ryan!
快 我走 M去
Come on. Inside. Come on, move.
- 你手上拿的是步 - 按我f的做 上翘 快
- Why do you have a rifle? - Just do what I say. Up the stairs, move.
躲M去
Get in the cabinet.
你槭颤N生我的
Why are you mad at me?
我不是生你的
I'm not mad at you. It's just...
你按我f的做 @很重要
It's just really important you do what I say.
你是好孩子
You're a good kid.
- 你f什N - ey
- What? - I said don't move.
考曼家的最後一人
The last Coxman.
我鹤釉谀
Where is my son?
治疫@行的人 可以你有一千N死法 但我]心思想那些
My business can get very creative, but I'm an old fashioned kind of guy.
我喜g胃咝
I like to keep things simple.
如果再我你一遍 我就把你指甲都拔下
So if I have to ask you again, I'm gonna pull out your fingernails...
把你手指都剁了 把你手o切了
cut off your fingers, chop off your hands...
把你鼻子o削了
and hack off your nose.
你肯定不
Oh, and that part about the nose,
喜g我那N值
you are really not gonna like that part.
你鹤硬恢档酶著你@N混蛋父H
You don't deserve your son.
把他抓到煅Y去
Take him to the garage.
混蛋
Bastard!
看到有孩子_著一台P雪去基W市了
Got a kid driving a snow blower headed towards Kehoe.
臀医o阿雅
Get a message...
信
to Aya.
告V我妻子
Tell my wife...
告V她...
tell her she's a...
特雷弗・卡柯 「S京」
你在质颤N
What are you doing?
@是我的工作
My job.